managementhelp.org 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy

## Description

This policy covers the website "Free Management Library" at [https://managementhelp.org](https://managementhelp.org/) and associated services (collectively the “Services”) that may be made available through use of the Website. The Website and the Services are owned and operated by Authenticity Consulting, LLC (“Authenticity”). After reading this policy, should you have privacy questions or concerns, send an email to [privacy@authenticityconsulting.com](mailto:privacy@authenticityconsulting.com).

This policy explains how we (as Authenticity) collect, protect and use information about visitors and users of our Website, including 1) non-personally identifiable information and also 2) personally identifiable information if visitors and users choose to provide it. It also explains how they can have that personal information changed or deleted if they desire. We collect and manage all of this information to make the Website and associated Services work better for our visitors and users.

## Your Implicit Agreement to This Policy

By visiting the Website or using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. Authenticity shall have right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy. If we makes material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, by means of a notice the next time you log in to the Website, or when you next utilize the associated Services. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice. You are responsible for reviewing the Website’s Data Privacy Policy periodically for any modification. Any access or use of the Website or Services by you after notice of modifications to this Policy shall constitute and be deemed to be your agreement to such modifications.

## Types of Information That We Collect

### Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to Provide

We get this type of information only if you choose to provide it. You can also opt out from, change or delete the information at any time. For example, you might provide your name and email address when you subscribe to a newsletter, share feedback to us or subscribe to a blog. You might also provide your postal address, phone number and credit/debit card numbers if you purchase a publication from us. You are responsible for the accuracy of the personal information, including updates or additions.

### Automatically Collected Non-Personally Identifiable Technical Information

#### Use of Cookies

In addition to the personal information you supply, we may automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable technical information. The technologies we may use to gather this information may include use of “cookies”.

Cookies are very small pieces of information a user's browser stores on the user's computer. We collect this information to (1) evaluate how visitors, guests, and customers use the Website and/or the Services; (2) evaluate the performance of our Website and Services, and (3) also provide you with personalized information if you opt in for that kind of information. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Please consult your browser instructions for information on how to modify your choices about cookies. If you modify your browser preferences, certain features of the Website may not be available to you.

#### Google Analytics Use of Cookies

The Website uses a tool called “Google Analytics” to improve the use of the Website. Google Analytics does not collect users' names or personally identifiable information (information that could be used to personally identify or contact you); it collects only the IP address from which the user accessed the Website. Google analyzes the activity from that address to record the user's time of the visit to the Website, time spent on its pages, the website where the user was referred from, and the user's type of browser and operating system. To collect that information, Google places a cookie on the user's computer. The cookies cannot be used by any organization other than Google. Description of how Google Analytics collects and processes this information is described at [How Google uses data when you use our partner's sites or apps](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Website is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

## How We Use Your Information

### For Improving Our Website and Services

IP addresses define the Internet location of computers and help us better understand the geographic distribution of our visitors and customers and manage the performance of the Website. Cookies are placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you visit the Website, so we can immediately recognize you when you return to the Website and deliver content specific to your interests. 

We may detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the Website and to understand the mix of browsers used by our visitors, guests, and customers. To learn about how people use our site, we examine various logs of IP usage information, which show the paths people take through the Website and how long they spend in certain areas.

When you use the Services, the Services may collect, in very general terms, your current physical location, your mobile device model number, your mobile device operating system version, and the time when you observed the images or other information provided by the Application. We use that information to ensure the Website and Services conform to the most commonly used devices and operating systems and the timing of their uses.

### For Marketing Purposes Only if You Opt-In

You can register (opt-in) on the Website or when using the Services to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. You can control your privacy preferences regarding such marketing communications (see the section below entitled “Your Privacy Preferences”).

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or promotions, and Authenticity may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or promotions. We use information collected from surveys and promotions to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers.

### Potential Provision to Third-Parties Only If Not Personal Marketing to You

You agree that we are authorized to use, reproduce and generally make such information available to third parties in the aggregate, provided that your information shall not include personally identifiable information about you or be attributable to you.

Authenticity may contract with unaffiliated third parties (e.g. Google) to provide services such as data hosting, advertising, analytics and other services. When we do this, we may provide your personally identifiable information to third parties only to provide those services, and they are explicitly not authorized to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.  
You agree that we are authorized to use, reproduce and generally make such information available to third parties in the aggregate, provided that your information shall not include personally identifiable information about you or be attributable to you.

## Use of the Website and Services by Children

THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES ARE NOT INTENDED FOR USE BY CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.

## How to Access, Correct or Delete Your Information

Send Authenticity an email at privacy@authenticityconsulting.com if you want to access, review, correct or delete your personally identifiable information collected by Authenticity. To protect your privacy and security, Authenticity will request certain personally identifiable information to verify your identity before granting you the right to access, review, make corrections or deletions to your personally identifiable information.

##  Disclosure of Information

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. It is also possible that Authenticity may sell one or more of its businesses. If so, then customer information, including your information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personal information, then you will be notified by an email sent to the last known email address in our files.

## Privacy of Other Websites and Services

The Website and/or the Services may contain links to other websites or other services Authenticity is not responsible for the privacy practices of those other sites or services. This policy only applies to information directly collected by Authenticity. 

## Amendments

Authenticity reserves the right to make amendments to the above information at any time, and such amendments will be in effect immediately.

Last Updated: June 25, 2018

## European Union ("EU") Users

If you are located in an EU country or jurisdiction, you might have additional rights as specified in the [EU General Data Protection Regulations](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation).

## Legal Address

Authenticity Consulting, LLC  
4008 Lake Drive Avenue North  
Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA
